articlepool.com 2011-05-20

# Article Pool - Privacy Policy

Home Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

  * We see serious importance in protecting you and your personal details.  

  * This Privacy Policy is designed to explain the manner in which **articlepool.com** collects, uses, and discloses the personal information provided by you as a result of the distribution of your article via our service  

  * **articlepool.com** reserves the right to change this policy at any time, without notice, by posting a new privacy policy at this location. The collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by **articlepool.com** will be governed by the version of this Policy in effect at that time. Please check this page periodically for any changes.   

  * In order for you to access certain materials or pages to make an purchase on this site requires that you provide certain personal information, including, but not limited to, your name and e-mail address. We use this information in order to contact you to provide you with further information about our company and services, as well as for other commercial and/or internal purposes such as market research in order to better understand the demographics of our Site visitors and potential customers and partners. We may share this information with our authorized partners and/or with third parties who act for or on behalf of us, but we do not otherwise provide or sell any information gathered on this Site to outside vendors.   

  * We collect the IP addresses of all visitors to our Site. We use your IP address in order to administer the Site, help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and for the "User Tracking" described above.  

  * In order to assist in protecting the confidentiality of your personal information, **articlepool.com** applies security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, in light of the nature of Internet technologies, security and privacy risks cannot be eliminated and, therefore, **articlepool.com** cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy.  

  * Keep reading the [Terms of Service](http://www.articlepool.com/termsofservice.html).
